

DARSHAK PATELIYA

():9327861612 ():7874066536

JR ENGINEER / CIVIL SUPERVISOR

G™ail:darshak.projects@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE:

A Jr Engineer / Civil Supervisor with 5 years of experience in infrastructure projects like residential, road and industrial, detailed knowledge in drawing and experience in site supervision. i worked well within team environment, safety and compliance issues are likewise include within my list of talent.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Hi-tech Contractors & Engineers - Ahmedabad- India April 2014 to July October 2014 (6 month)

Posted as a Trainee Engineer and work responsibility

- Testing in laboratory for RCC
- Additional responsibility as a quality control engineer
- Complete layout measuring dimension such, height, length, distance between the reference point
- Set project goals and oversee projects to completion; schedule and track assignments.
- Sardar Patel College of Engineering as a July 2015 to May 2017 (1.9 Years) Posted as a Lab Assistant
 - Teaching practicals to all students.
 - On site practical like RCC ,Geotech, Survey Engineering.
- Knowledge Institute of Technology (KITE) July 2017 to December 2018 (1.5 Years).

Posted as a Lab Assistant

- Teaching practicals to all students.
- On site practical like Concrete Technology, Basic Civil Technology, Surveying, Geotechnics and Applied Geology, Soil Mechanics, Highway Engineering.

Sahajanand Shrusti Construction VV Nagar -India Jan 2019 to Dec 2020
(2 Years

Posted as a Site Supervisor and work responsibility

- Oversee site supervison
- Advance daily planing to maximize available resources
- Supervise sub contractors and other labor workers
- Preparing and presenting site inductions, safety briefings and toolbox talks
- Completing records for site
- Drainage and Roadline
- ❖ Kaira Can Company Ltd, Kanjari -India Jan-01 2021 to August 2021 (8 Months) Post as a Client Civil Engineer and work responsibility
 - As per drawing supervison and checking.
 - Daily Reporting to A.G.M
 - Co-Ordination with Sub Contractor and Engineers
 - Final authority to Pass Bill after work completed.
 - Materials checking as per bill and as per mentioned in Tender.
 - Preparing and presenting site inductions, safety briefings and toolbox talks.
 - Completing records for site reports.
- GIDC Bharuch (Water Supply Department)- September 2021 to Till Date Posted as an AAE (Additional Assistant Engineer)
 - Giving approval of Water Connection.
 - Checking Documents related water supply connection.
 - Onsite supervision of Water Connection related work.
 - Daily Reporting to DEE (W/S)

EDUCATION QUALIFICATION:

- Diploma in Civil Engineering Gujarat Technological University pass year 2015 with 6.89 CGPA
- CCC Computer Course with Nice Computer Institute in Vvnagar pass year 2013 with B grade
- B.E Degree of Civil Engineering (Pursuing / Last Sem..)

CORE COMPETENCIES: Team Player, Problem Solving, Decision Maker, Positive and Learner.

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Date of Birth: 31 -12-1992

Address: At:Dabhsar, Ta:Galteshwar, Di:Kheda, Gujarat, India - 388250

Language Known: English, Hindi, Gujarati

Hobby: Travelling, Book Reading.